Adults dream during REM (rapid eye movement) sleep and infants have loads of REM.
成年人在快速眼动（REM）睡眠期间做梦，而婴儿有大量的快速眼动睡眠。
So, it might be fair to assume that babies have tons of dreams.
因此，认为婴儿会做很多梦，或许也说得过去。
But scientists believe REM serves a completely different purpose for newborns and infants than dreaming.
但科学家认为，对新生儿和婴儿来说，快速眼动睡眠的作用完全不同，并不是用来做梦。
In babies, REM allows the brain to develop pathways and connections and, eventually, learn languages.
在婴儿身上，快速眼动睡眠让大脑得以形成通路和连接，并最终学会语言。
Since your baby doesn’t dream at this stage of brain development, it’s safe to assume babies do not have nightmares, either.
由于你的宝宝在大脑发育的这个阶段不做梦，可以有把握地认为，宝宝也不会做噩梦。
Nightmares stem from exposure to trauma, an overactive imagination, and the normal stresses of everyday life.
噩梦源于遭受创伤、过度活跃的想象力以及日常生活中常有的压力。
Are you wondering what babies dream about?
你是不是想知道宝宝会梦到些什么？
Good question, but the answer is nothing!
问得好，不过答案是：什么也梦不到！
So, when do babies start dreaming?
那么，宝宝从什么时候开始做梦呢？
The general consensus is that they start dreaming around the age of two.
普遍的共识是，他们大约在两岁时开始做梦。
Psychologist David Foulkes studies children (from very small kids to teens) to bring the secrets of their dreams to the light of day.
心理学家戴维·福克斯研究儿童（从很小的孩子到青少年），以揭开他们梦境的秘密。
In his lab, he lets kids fall asleep and then wakes them 3 times a night and asks them to describe what they recall.
在他的实验室里，他让孩子们入睡，然后每晚把他们叫醒3次，请他们描述自己记得的内容。
Foulkes’ findings are unsurprising.
福克斯的研究结果并不出人意料。
Basically, little kids have little dreams.
总的来说，小孩子做的梦也小。
But exactly what kids see while dreaming depends on their age.
但孩子在梦中究竟看到什么，取决于他们的年龄。
As children develop and grow, their dreams do too.
随着孩子的发育和成长，他们的梦也在发展。
Dreams of very small kids are usually just snapshots, looking much more like a slideshow than a movie, when compared to the dreams of adults.
与成年人的梦相比，很小的孩子的梦通常只是一些快照，看起来与其说像电影，不如说更像幻灯片放映。
They heavily feature animals and other familiar sights, like images of people eating.
这些梦里大量出现动物和其他熟悉的景象，比如人们吃东西的画面。
According to Foulkes, “Children’s dream life…seems to be similar to their waking imagination and narration.”
按照福克斯的说法，“孩子们的梦境生活……似乎与他们清醒时的想象和叙述相似。”
Kids ages 5–9 begin seeing moving images and characters in action.
5至9岁的孩子开始梦到活动的画面和动起来的人物。
Dreams now include multiple events strung together, one after the other.
这时的梦里有多个事件，一个接一个地串在一起。
Kids also start developing greater ability to remember dreams.
孩子们也开始具备更强的记梦能力。
Still, that’s not always the case: When roused during REM sleep, 25% of the kids in Foulkes’ studies had no recollection of dreaming, a trend that continues through age 9.
不过，情况并非总是如此：在福克斯的研究中，25%的孩子在快速眼动睡眠期间被唤醒时，不记得自己做过梦，这种趋势一直持续到9岁。
So, if your baby seems to be in a stressed state while sleeping or is upset upon waking, there may be other factors at play.
因此，如果你的宝宝睡觉时似乎处于紧张状态，或者醒来时情绪不安，那可能是其他因素在起作用。